# MAHMOUD SAAD

WEB DEVELOPER

+20 1279119364

✓ 101mahm0udsaad@gmail.com

2 1 Elmadina St.,Omrania - Giza

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ma hmoud-saad-12174a234/

https://github.com/mahm0udsaad

## SUMMARY

I'm not your typical web developer. I have experience in web3 and I've worked with TensorFlow.js and AI modules. I enjoy creating unique solutions and take care of every part of my projects, including building the back end and scraping data from websites. I'm not afraid to think outside the box, and I approach every project with creativity and a positive attitude. You can trust that I'll bring the same dedication and innovation to your project.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- Figma
- CSS3
- Tailwindcss
- JavaScript
- Next Js
- React
- Node Js

## SKILLS

- · Strong Problem-solving
- Analytical Skills
- Interpersonal Skills
- Communication
- Collaboration
- · Continuously Learning
- Critical Thinking
- Attention to details

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **EL-SEWEDY AUTOMATION**

Software Developer - 2023 - Present

- Collaborate with Content maneger to identify and prioritize features and requirements
- Troubleshoot and resolve Website defects and issues

#### **TWOSOFT**

Software Developer - 2023 - Present

- Rebuilt Website with new technologies
- User Experience

#### VIVO

Promoter - Jan 2019-Jul 2020

- Vivo Promoter
- Customer Engagement
- Sales Expertise

## EDUCATION

#### **HELWAN UNIVERSITY**

Business Administration - English Section

2020 - 2024

# CIRTIFICATIONS

#### **UDACITY**

FullStack Web Development Track

Nov 2020 - Jan 2020